<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EggHuntChecklist</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_1">The tradition of decorating eggs dates back to ancient civilizations, including Egyptians and Persians.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_2">The largest Easter egg ever made was over 7 meters tall and weighed over 3,600 kilograms.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_3">In some cultures, eggs are painted red to symbolize the blood of Christ.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_4">The Easter Bunny originated from German folklore, where it was believed to lay eggs for children to find.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_5">In 1970, the first-ever Easter egg hunt was held on the White House lawn.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_6">Cadbury\'s Crème Egg is one of the most popular Easter treats, with over 200 million sold each year.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_7">In Finland, Easter is celebrated with a tradition where children dress up as witches and go door-to-door for treats.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_8">The word "Easter" is believed to be derived from "Eostre," a pagan goddess of spring and fertility.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_9">In Ukraine, the art of decorating eggs is known as "Pysanky," which involves intricate designs using wax and dye.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_10">The tradition of the Easter egg hunt is thought to symbolize the search for the tomb of Jesus.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_11">In Greece, red eggs are cracked against each other in a game called "tsougrisma," symbolizing the resurrection.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_12">The practice of giving chocolate eggs started in the 19th century in Europe.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_13">The world\'s most expensive chocolate egg, made by a luxury chocolatier, was valued at over €144,000.</string>
    <string name="easter_fact_14">In some cultures, Easter eggs are hidden in gardens and parks for children to find, promoting outdoor activity.</string>
    <string name="screen_title">Egg Hunt Checklist</string>
    <string name="screen_subtitle">Pick locations, where you’ve found eggs</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="oops_the_egg_rolled_away">Oops, the egg rolled away!</string>
    <string name="easter_fact">Easter fact!</string>
</resources>